Q1:  What task does the method value_counts perform?

a. Returns summary statistics
b. Returns counts of unique values
c. Returns the first five columns of a dataframe

Correct. Returns counts of unique values

Q2: What does the horizontal axis in a scatter plot represent?

a. Independent variable
b. Dependent variable

Correct. Independent variable

Q3: If we have 10 columns and 100 samples, how large is the output of df.corr()?

a. 10 x 100
b. 10x10
c. 100x100

Correct. 10x10

Q4: If the Pearson Correlation between two variables is zero, then ...

a. The two variables have zero mean
b. The two variables are not correlated

Correct. The two variables are not correlated

Q5: Consider the following dataframe:

df_test = df[['body-style', 'price']]
The following operation is applied:

df_grp = df_test.groupby(['body-style'], as_index=False).mean()

What are the resulting values of: df_grp[‘price’]?

a. The average price for each body style
b. The average price
c. The average body style

Correct. The average price for each body style

Q6: What is the minimum possible value of Pearson's Correlation?

a. 1
b. -100
c. -1

Correct. -1

Q7: What is the Pearson Correlation between variables X and Y, if X=Y?

a. -1
b. 1
c. 0

Correct. 1
